Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Central Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Central Files
  - 2004/2005
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Graduate Student Instructors (GSI) (Box 496)
      - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) (Box 496)
      - Graham, Don (Box 496)
      - Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) (Box 496)
      - Health Science Council (HSC) (Box 496)
      - Henry Russel Lecture (Box 496)
      - Higher Education (Box 496)
      - Honorary Degree (Box 496)
      - Hospitals and Health Centers Executive Board (HHCEB), 10 volumes, 1 folder (Box 496)
      - Housing (Box 496)
      - Human Resources and Affirmative Action (HRAA), 4 folders
        - Folders 1-2 (Box 496)
          - Supervisor's Toolkit
            [Executive records restricted until July 1, 2025 ]
        - Folders 3-4 (Box 497)
      - Immigration Task Force (Box 497)
      - Information Technology, 3 folders (Box 497)
      - Information Technology Central Services (ITCS) (Box 497)
      - Information Technology Security Council (Box 497)
      - Institute of Gerontology (Box 497)
      - Institute for Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR)
        - General (Box 497)
        - Director Review (Box 508)
      - Institute for Social Research (ISR)
        - General (Box 497)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
      - Institutional Equity
        - General (Box 497)
        - Complaints (Box 508)
      - Intellectual Property (Box 497)
      - International
        - General (Box 497)
        - Students (Box 508)
      - International Institute
        - General, 2 folders (Box 497)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
      - Kellogg (Box 497)
      - "Kook Mail" (Box 497)
      - Lawsuit (Box 497)
      - Lecturers Employee Organization (LEO) (Box 497)
      - Life Sciences, Values and Society Program (LSVSP) (Box 497)
      - M-Prime (Box 497)
      - Master Plan (Box 497)
      - Media Union (Box 497)
      - Medical Affairs (Box 497)
      - Medical Center
        - General (Box 497)
        - Hospital Budget (Box 497)
      - Mellon Foundation (Box 497)
      - Mental Health Research Institute (MHRI) (Box 497)
      - Michigan Administrative Information System (MAIS) (Box 497)
      - Michigan Student Assembly (MSA) (Box 498)
      - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities (MUCIA) (Box 498)
      - Millennium (Box 498)
      - Multicultural Affairs (Box 498)
      - Museum of Art (UMMA) (Box 498)
      - Nanoscience Building (Box 498)
      - National Association of State Universities Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 498)
      - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 498)
      - National Survey of Student Engagement (NSSE) (Box 498)
      - National Tragedies (Box 498)
      - Neuroscience (Box 498)
      - New Student Programs (Box 498)
      - News and Information (Box 498)
      - North Campus (Box 498)
      - Office of Academic Affairs (OAA) 6+1, 4 folders (Box 498)
      - Parking (Box 498)
      - Peer Institutions (Box 498)
      - President (Box 498)
      - Presidential Initiative Fund (Box 498)
      - Presidential Initiatives
        - General (Box 498)
        - Committee on Multidisciplinary Education and Team Teaching (Box 498)
        - Committee on the Prototype for Rational and Affordable Health Care (Box 498)
        - Committee on Reconnection of Student Residential and Academic Life (Box 498)
        - Committee on University Scholarship on Ethical Issues in the Public Domain (Box 498)
        - Presidential Initiative on Healthy Living (Box 498)
      - President's Council (Box 498)
      - Program in the Environment (PITE) (Box 498)
      - Promotions
        - General (Box 498)
        - Faculty (Box 508)
      - Proposals (Box 498)
      - Provost's Advisory Committee on Education and Evaluation of Responsible Research and Scholarship (Box 498)
      - Provost's Advisory Committee on Education for a Diverse Democracy (Box 498)
      - Provost's Advisory Committee on Faculty (Box 498)
      - Provost's Council on Student Honors (PCSH) (Box 498)
      - Provost's Faculty Advisory Committee (PFAC) (Box 498)
      - Provost's Faculty Initiative Program (PFIP) (Box 508)
      - Provost's Advisory Council on Women's Initiatives (PACWI) (Box 498)
      - Public Goods (Box 498)
      - Recreational Sports (Box 498)
      - Regents
        - Approval of Personnel Matters (Box 498)
        - Bylaw Revisions (Box 498)
        - Communications, 3 folders (Box 499)
        - Conversation Notes (Box 499)
        - Correspondence
          - General (Box 499)
          - Searches (Box 508)
          - Students (Box 508)
        - E-mails to Regents (Box 499)
        - General Communications (Box 499)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 499)
        - Symposia Ideas (Box 499)
      - Registrar, 2 folders (Box 499)
      - Requests, 3 folders (Box 499)
      - Research
        - General (Box 499)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
        - Misconduct (Box 508)
      - Residency
        - General (Box 499)
        - Students (Box 508)
      - Residential College (Box 499)
      - Residential Life, 4 folders
        - Folders 1-2 (Box 499)
        - Folders 3-4 (Box 500)
      - Rhodes Scholarship (Box 500)
      - "Roads Scholars" (Box 500)
      - Science, Technology and Public Policy (Box 500)
      - Sea Grant (Box 500)
      - Searches
        - Education (Box 508)
        - Institute for Social Research (ISR) (Box 508)
        - Rackham Dean Search (Box 508)
        - Vice President for Research (Box 508)
      - Secretary of the University (Box 508)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 500)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 4 folders (Box 500)
      - Sexual Orientation, 2 folders (Box 500)
      - Society of Fellows (Box 500)
      - Standard Practice Guidelines (SPG) (Box 500)
      - Students
        - General (Box 500)
        - Complaints (Box 500)
        - Deceased (Box 500)
      - Student Affairs, 2 folders (Box 500)
      - Student and Exchange Visitor Information System (SEVIS) (Box 500)
      - Student-Parent Task Force (Box 500)
      - Student Recruitment (Box 500)
      - Surveys (Box 500)
      - Team Teaching Task Force (Box 500)
      - Technology Transfer (Box 500)
      - Tenure (Box 500)
      - Thurnau Professors (Box 500)
      - Tuition (Box 500)
      - Undergraduate Council (Box 500)
      - Undergraduate Teaching (Box 500)
      - University Library
        - General (Box 500)
        - Google Books Digitization (Box 500)
      - University Musical Society (Box 501)
      - University Press (Box 501)
      - Whitaker Foundation (Box 501)
      - Women (Box 501)
      - Zell Lurie Institute (Box 501)
    - Schools and Colleges Files
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, School of
        - General (Box 501)
        - Appointments and Promotions (Box 508)
      - Art and Design, School of
        - General (Box 501)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
      - Business Administration, School of
        - General (Box 501)
        - Appointments and Promotions (Box 508)
        - Grievance (Box 508)
      - Dearborn Campus (Box 501)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - General (Box 501)
        - Promotion and Retention (Box 508)
      - Education, School of
        - General (Box 501)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
        - Ball, Deborah (Box 508)
        - Nidiffer, Jana-Tenure (Box 508)
        - Raudenbush Retention (Box 508)
        - Personnel Matter (Box 508)
      - Engineering, College of
        - General (Box 501)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
        - Strategic Plan (Box 501)
        - Students (Box 508)
      - Flint Campus (Box 501)
      - Information, School of
        - General (Box 501)
        - Kellogg Foundation (Box 501)
        - Recruitment (Box 508)
      - Kinesiology Division (Box 501)
      - Law School
        - General (Box 501)
        - Faculty and Appointments (Box 508)
      - Life Sciences Institute (LSI)
        - General, 3 folders (Box 501)
        - LSI Appointments (Box 508)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - General, 3 folders (Box 502)
        - Appointments and Retention (Box 508)
      - Medical School
        - General, 2 folders (Box 502)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
      - Music, School of
        - General (Box 502)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
        - Grievances (Box 508)
      - Natural Resources and the Environment, School of
        - General (Box 502)
        - External Advisory Committee (Box 502)
        - Michigan Sea Grant (Box 502)
        - Recruitment (Box 508)
      - Nursing, School of
        - General (Box 502)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
        - Students (Box 508)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - General (Box 502)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
      - Public Health, School of
        - General (Box 502)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
        - Dean Search (Box 508)
        - New Building, 2001-2003 (Box 502)
        - Self-Study Report, 2 folders (Box 502)
      - Public Policy, School of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 502)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
      - Rackham Graduate School
        - General (Box 502)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
      - Social Work, School of
        - General (Box 502)
        - Appointments (Box 508)
    - Chronological Files
      - September 2004-April 2005, 4 folders (Box 583)
      - May-August 2005, 2 folders (Box 584)
  - 2005/2006
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Academic Affairs
        - General, 2 folders (Box 509)
          [Executive records restricted until July 01, 2026 ]
        - Advisory Committee (Box 509)
        - Budget (Box 509)
        - CIAR Review (Box 575)
          [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2036 ]
        - Provost Search (Box 575)
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Committee (Box 509)
      - Academic Governing Board (AGB) (Box 509)
      - Academic Program Group (APG), 2 folders (Box 509)
      - Academic Program Group Development (APGD) (Box 509)
      - Accreditation (Box 509)
      - Admissions
        - General (Box 509)
        - Spencer, Theodore (Box 575)
      - ADVANCE (Box 509)
      - Affiliation Agreements, 5 folders (Box 509)
      - Alumni (Box 509)
      - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) (Box 509)
      - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 509)
      - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS) CyberCommission level3 (Box 509)
      - Arts of Citizenship (Box 509)
      - Arts @ Michigan (Box 509)
      - Associate Provosts (Box 509)
      - Association of American Colleges and Universities (AACU) (Box 509)
      - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 509)
      - Athletics (Box 509)
      - Audits, 2 folders (Box 510)
      - Awards (Box 510)
      - Benefits (Box 510)
      - Bentley Historical Library
        - General (Box 510)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
      - Botanical Gardens (Box 510)
      - Budget
        - General, 3 folders (Box 510)
        - State Budget Request (Box 510)
        - Budget and Planning, 3 folders (Box 510)
      - Calendar (Box 510)
      - Campaign (Box 510)
      - Campus Safety (Box 510)
      - Capital Projects (Box 510)
      - Carnegie (Box 510)
      - Center for Advancing Research and Societal Solutions (CARSS) (Box 510)
      - Center for the Education of Women (CEW) (Box 510)
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 510)
      - China
        - General (Box 511)
        - Background-UM in China (Box 511)
        - Issues (Box 511)
        - Mary Sue Coleman Invitation (Box 511)
        - Michigan-China University Leadership Forum, 3 folders (Box 511)
        - Peking University Joint Institute (Box 511)
        - Shanghai Jiao Tong University (SJTU) Joint Institute (Box 511)
        - Trip Planning (Box 511)
        - Trip Proposals and Agreements (Box 511)
      - Clements Library (Box 575)
      - Commencement (Box 511)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC)
        - General (Box 511)
        - Engaged Institution Initiative (Box 511)
      - Communications (Box 511)
      - Community Relations (Box 511)
      - Compensation (Box 511)
      - Conflict of Interest/Commitment (Box 511)
      - Constitution Day, 2 folders (Box 511)
      - Convocation (Box 511)
      - Delegation of Authority (Box 511)
      - Depression Center (Box 511)
      - Detroit (Box 511)
      - Detroit Observatory (Box 511)
      - Development, 7 folders (Box 512)
      - Distinguished University Professors (Box 512)
      - Diversity, 2 folders (Box 512)
      - Dual Career (Box 575)
      - Economic Forecasting, 2 folders (Box 512)
      - Economic Impact (Box 512)
      - Enrollment (Box 512)
      - Environment (Box 512)
      - Ethics in Public Life Task Force (Box 512)
      - Executive Officers, 5 folders (Box 512)
      - Events (Box 513)
      - Facilities (Box 513)
      - Faculty, 2 folders (Box 513)
      - Family Friendly Policies (Box 513)
      - Finance VP Area (Box 513)
      - Financial Aid
        - General (Box 513)
        - Staff Salaries (Box 575)
        - Students (Box 575)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2091 ]
      - Financial Reports (Box 513)
      - FOIA (Freedom of Information Act) (Box 513)
      - Foundations (Box 513)
      - Gender Equity (Box 575)
      - Gender in Science and Engineering (GSE) (Box 513)
      - General Counsel
        - General (Box 513)
        - Cases (Box 575)
          [Patient/client records restricted until July 01, 2106 ]
      - Government Relations (Box 513)
      - Government: State (Box 513)
      - Graduate Employee Organization (GEO) (Box 513)
      - Graduate Student Instructors (Box 513)
      - Graham, Donald/Graham Environmental Sustainability Institute
        - General, 3 folders (Box 513)
        - Director Search (Box 575)
      - Great Lakes Program (Box 513)
      - Hospitals and Health Centers Executive Board (HHCEB), 7 folders (Box 513)
      - Health Science Council (Box 514)
      - Health Service (Box 514)
      - Health System (Box 514)
        - Victors
          (Includes the University of Michigan Health System commercials.)
          [Executive records restricted until July 1, 2026 ]
      - Henry Russel (Box 514)
      - Higher Education (Box 514)
      - Honorary Degrees (Box 514)
      - Housing (Box 514)
      - Human Resources and Affirmative Action (HRAA), 2 folders (Box 514)
      - Human Resources Management System (HRMS) (Box 514)
      - Immigration Task Force (Box 514)
      - Information Technology
        - General (Box 514)
        - Com Info Tech Communications (Box 514)
        - Security Council (Box 514)
      - ITCS Info Tech Central Services (Box 514)
      - Institutes (Box 514)
      - International
        - General, 2 folders (Box 514)
        - Agreements (Box 514)
        - L'Universite De Provence (Box 575)
      - Invitations, 3 folders (Box 514)
      - Knight Collaboration (Box 514)
      - Kook Mail (Box 514)
      - Lawsuit (Box 575)
      - Lecturers' Employee Organization (LEO) (Box 514)
      - Michigan Administrative Information Systems (MAIS) (Box 514)
      - Martin Luther King (Box 514)
      - Media Union (Box 514)
      - Medical Affairs
        - General (Box 514)
        - Executive Vice President for Medical Affairs (EVPMA) (Box 514)
      - Medical Center (Box 514)
      - Mellon (Box 515)
      - Millennium Project (Box 515)
      - Museum of Art, 2 folders (Box 515)
      - National Survey of Student Engagement (NSSE) (Box 515)
      - National Tragedies
        - General (Box 515)
        - Faculty (Box 575)
        - Students (Box 515)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2091; remove to Box 575]
      - Neurosciences (Box 515)
      - News and Information Services (Box 515)
      - New Student Programs (Box 515)
      - North Campus (Box 515)
      - Office of Academic Affairs (OAA) 6+1 (Box 515)
      - Ombudsman (Box 515)
      - Parking (Box 515)
      - Peer Institutions, 2 folders (Box 515)
      - Polish/Poland (Box 515)
      - President
        - General (Box 515)
        - Staff level4 (Box 515)
      - President's Initiatives
        - MHealthy Communities Initiative (Box 515)
      - Professoriate (Box 515)
      - Promotions
        - General (Box 515)
        - Promotion Cases (Box 575)
      - Proposals
        - General (Box 515)
        - Reynolds, Thomas (Box 515)
      - Provost's Council on Student Honors (Box 515)
      - Provost's Faculty Initiatives Program (PFIP) (Box 575)
      - Rec Sports (Box 515)
      - Recommendations for Healthy U (Box 515)
      - Regents
        - General, 3 folders (Box 515)
          - Presentation to the Regents, April 21, 2006
            (Includes the presentation by Dean of the Ross School of Business, Robert J. Dolan, to the University of Michigan Regents.)
        - Communications
          - General (Box 515)
          - A-H (Box 515)
          - I-P (Box 516)
          - R-Z (Box 516)
      - Registrar (Box 516)
      - Requests, 2 folders (Box 516)
      - Research
        - General, 3 folders (Box 516)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
        - Budget, 2 folders (Box 516)
        - Directorship-Compliance (Box 575)
        - IRB Investigations (Box 575)
      - ROTC (Box 516)
      - Residency (Box 516)
      - Residential Life (Box 516)
      - Rhodes
        - General (Box 516)
        - Student Applications (Box 575)
      - Road Scholars (Box 516)
      - Royalty and Patent, 2003-2004 (Box 516)
      - Salary (Box 516)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 7 folders
        - Folders 1-6 (Box 516)
        - Folder 7 (Box 517)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 517)
      - Sexual Orientation
        - General, 2 folders (Box 517)
        - General Counsel (Box 575)
        - LGBT (Box 517)
      - Society of Fellows (Box 517)
      - Standard Practice Guides (SPG) (Box 517)
      - Students
        - General (Box 517)
        - Complaints (Box 575)
        - Deceased (Box 517)
      - Student Affairs
        - General (Box 517)
        - Student Grievances (Box 575)
      - Student Parent Task Force (Box 517)
      - Surveys (Box 517)
      - Team Teaching Task Force (Box 517)
      - Technology Tech Transfer (Box 517)
      - Tenure (Box 517)
      - Thurnau Professors (Box 517)
      - Tuition (Box 517)
      - University of Michigan Transportation Research Institute (UMTRI) (Box 575)
      - University Press, 2 folders (Box 517)
      - University Library, 2 folders (Box 517)
      - University Musical Society (Box 517)
      - University Unions (Box 517)
        - Funding Model
      - Washington Office (Box 517)
      - Washington Semester (Box 517)
      - Whitaker Foundation (Box 517)
      - Women (Box 517)
      - Zell Lurie Institute (Box 517)
    - Schools and Colleges
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
        - General (Box 517)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
        - Budget (Box 517)
        - Grievance (Box 575)
      - Art and Design, School of
        - General (Box 517)
        - Faculty (Box 575)
      - Business, School of
        - General (Box 517)
        - Faculty (Box 575)
      - Dearborn (Box 517)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - General (Box 517)
        - Executive Committee, 1992-2006 (Box 517)
        - Faculty (Box 575)
      - Education, School of
        - General (Box 517)
        - Executive Committee, 1991-2005 (Box 518)
        - Faculty (Box 575)
      - Engineering, College of
        - General (Box 518)
        - Executive Committee, 1991-2005 (Box 518)
        - Appointments and Retention (Box 575)
        - Dean Search (Box 575)
        - Grievances (Box 575)
      - Flint (Box 518)
        - Imagine: The UM-Flint Difference
      - Institute for Social Research
        - General (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
      - Information, School of
        - General (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
      - International Institute (Box 518)
      - Kinesiology, Division of
        - General (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
      - Law School
        - General (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
        - Building (Box 518)
      - Life Sciences Institute (LSI)
        - General (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
      - Medical School
        - General (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
        - Salary Study (Box 518)
      - Music, School of
        - General (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
        - Dean Search (Box 575)
        - Name Change (Box 518)
      - Natural Resources and Environment, School of
        - General (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
        - Environmental Reporting for the Ann Arbor Campus (Box 518)
        - Strategic Assessment (Box 518)
      - Nursing, School of
        - General (Box 518)
        - Accreditation (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - General (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
      - Public Policy, School of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 518)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
        - Ford School Building Meeting, 1/21/02 (Box 519)
        - New Building (Box 519)
        - Student (Box 575)
      - Rackham Graduate Studies
        - General (Box 519)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
        - Discovery Process (Box 519)
      - Social Work, School of
        - General (Box 519)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
        - Student (Box 575)
    - Chronological Files
      - September 2005-August 2006, 6 folders (Box 584)
  - 2006/2007
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Academic Affairs
        - General, 2 folders (Box 519)
          [Executive records restricted until July 01, 2027 ]
        - Appointments (Box 575)
          [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2037 ]
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Committee (AAAC), 2 folders (Box 519)
      - Academic Program Group (APG), 6 folders (Box 519)
      - Academic Program Group Development (APGD), 2 folders (Box 519)
      - Accreditation
        - General (Box 520)
        - Student Learning Assessment (Box 520)
      - Admissions
        - General, 2 folders (Box 520)
        - Students (Box 575)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2092 ]
      - ADVANCE
        - General (Box 520)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
        - Assessing the Academic Work Environment for Women Scientists & Engineers (Box 520)
      - Affiliation Agreements
        - General (Box 520)
        - July 2006 (Box 520)
        - August 2006 (Box 520)
        - September 2006 (Box 520)
        - October 2006 (Box 520)
        - November 2006 (Box 520)
        - December 2006 (Box 520)
        - January 2007 (Box 520)
        - February 2007 (Box 520)
        - March 2007 (Box 520)
        - April 2007 (Box 520)
        - May 2007 (Box 520)
        - June 2007 (Box 520)
      - African Studies Committee (Box 520)
      - Alumni (Box 520)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (AAAS) (Box 520)
      - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 520)
      - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS) (Box 520)
      - Arboretum (Box 520)
      - Arts of Citizenship (Box 520)
      - Association of American Colleges and Universities (AACU) (Box 520)
      - Association of American Universities (AAU)
        - General (Box 520)
        - Appointments (Box 575)
      - Association of Governing Boards (AGB) (Box 520)
      - Athletics (Box 521)
      - Audits
        - General, 2 folders (Box 521)
        - Audit Reports (Box 575)
      - Awards, 2 folders (Box 521)
      - Benefits
        - General (Box 521)
        - Benefits Advisory Committee, 2 folders (Box 521)
        - MCare Project (Box 521)